## M.M Tharindu Gunathilaka

## **Senior Software Engineer**



## **Contact**

### Address:

No: 220/B, Anguruwamulla, Eheliyagoda.

#### Phone:

070-4369 903 / 077-5438 315

#### **Email:**

tharindumananjaya@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tharindu-gunathilaka-a003b887/

## GitHub:

https://github.com/tharindutmg

#### About me:

https://tharindutmg.github.io/mywebsite/

## Referees

## Mr. Manjula Kumara,

Tech Lead - Software Engineering, Mobitel (Pvt) Ltd,

E-mail: manjulas@mobitel.lk

Mobile: 071-5989291

#### Mr. W.T.S.D Abeygunawardhane,

Project Manager,

Intellect Design Arena LTD,No: 123, Bauddhaloka Mawatha, 2nd Floor.

#### E-mail:

thushanka.a@intellectdesign.com / sridinindu@gmail.com

Mobile: 0714355920 / 0727819600

# **Summary**

Full stack web developer experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Since February 2014 I have 7 years plus professional experience in software design, development, implementing and deployment standalone and web based solutions in Java EE Technologies.

## **Technical skills**

Development Languages: Java/ J2SE/ J2EE (JSP, Servlet)

• Framework : Spring/Spring Boot, Struts, Hibernate

• Web services : RESTful Web Services

• Front End: Angular 2/Angular JS, JavaScript, HTML, Css

• DMS: MySQL, IBM informix, Oracle

• Server : Apache Tomcat, Wamp, Jboss , Weblogic

• Build Tools : Apache Maven

• Operating Systems : Windows, Ubuntu, Linux Mint

Version Control: SVN,GIT, BITBUCKET

• Proficient IDEs: Eclipse/STS, NetBeans, IntelliJ idea

## **Academic Qualification**

Completed **Degree** of **BSc** (Hons) Computing Awarded by **Wrexham Glyndwr University**, UUGC Recognized **British Government Public University**.

Completed **Higher National Diploma** in Information Technology in Sri Lanka Institute of Advanced Technological Education **(SLIATE)**-Naiwala.

# **Working Experience**

- Senior Software Engineer at Allion Technologies (Pvt) Limited. present
- Software engineer at Lanka Solution (Pvt) Ltd. 2019 2021
   Mobitel (Pvt) Ltd as outsource software engineer.
- Associate Software Engineer at OpenArc System Management (pvt)

Ltd. - 2014-2019

Associate Software Engineer - 2017 to 2019

Software Developer - 2015 to 2017

Trainee software developer- 2014 to 2015

.

# **Project Experience**

### **OPEN ARC**

• **SkyBank(Core banking solution)** - OpenArc Systems Management (Pvt.) Ltd Totally integrated, browser-based software solution for Merchant Banks and Finance Companies. This project contains some modules as Corpdata, Lending, Leasing, Loan, Hire Purchase, Funding, Savings, Deposit, Teller and General Ledger.

Languages : Java EE, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, XML

Frameworks : Hibernate, Spring, Struts

Databases : Oracle database

Server : Tomcat

Tools : Eclipse/Spring tool suit

#### MOBITEL

VAMS - Vendor Authentication and application Management System

Languages : Java EE, Angular 2, Bootstrap 4, ngx-bootstrap

Frameworks : Spring boot, Spring security, JWT

Databases : Oracle 19c Server : JBoss

Version control : Bitbucket, Jenkins
Tools : Eclipse/Spring tool suit

• **Repair Return System** - Repairing anything usually requires some kind of parts and the consumption of those parts need to be managed to correctly track the assets. Repair Return Management system includes option in system to track the defected repairing assets.

Languages : Java EE, Angular 2, Bootstrap

Frameworks : Spring boot
Databases : My SQL
Server : JBoss
Version control : Bitbucket

Tools : Eclipse/Spring tool suit

• SUPPORTAPP - Internal Staff Support

Languages : Java EE, Angular 2, Bootstrap 4
Frameworks : Spring boot, Jdbc Template

Databases : Oracle Database 19c,IBM Informix, MySQL 8.0

Server : Oracle WebLogic 12c, Version control : Bitbucket, Jenkins Tools : Eclipse/Spring tool suit